Cheri, Cheri Lady
Oh I cannot explain every time it's the same
More I feel that it's real take my heart
I've been lonely to long oh
I can't be so strong
Take the chance for romance take my heart
I need you so there's no time
I'll ever go
Cheri cheri lady going through emotion
Love is where you find it listen to your heart
Cheri cheri lady living in devotion
It's always like the first time let me take a part
Cheri Cheri lady like there's no tomorrow
Take my heart, don't lose it listen to your heart
Cheri cheri lady to know you is to love you
If you call me baby
I'll be always yours
I get up
I get down all my world turns around
Who is right who is wrong
I dont know
I've got pain in my heart got some love in my soul easy come but
I think easy go
I need you so although times
I move so slow
Cheri cheri lady going through emotion
Love is where you find it listen to your heart
Cheri cheri lady living in devotion
It's always like the first time let me take a part
Cheri Cheri lady like there's no tomorrow
Take my heart, don't lose it listen to your heart
Cheri cheri lady to know you is to love you
If you call me baby
I'll be always yours
Cheri Cheri lady like there's no tomorrow
Take my heart, don't lose it listen to your heart
Cheri cheri lady to know you is to love you
If you call me baby
I'll be always yours
Cheri Cheri lady like there's no tomorrow
Take my heart, don't lose it listen to your heart
Cheri cheri lady to know you is to love you
If you call me baby
I'll be always yours